(234) 906-3972-264 melodyomopelola@gmail.com

MELODY OMOPELOLA OGUNFEIBO

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Having a profound passion for enhancing the lives of individuals with their different age range and categories, I bring a therapeutic and compassionate touch to care and an administrative acumen. Skilled in providing personalized care, companionship, therapy/rehabilitation, massage and relaxation, encouragement, support, exercise and lifestyle changes. Also collaborating with healthcare professionals. My goal is to utilize my unique blend of skills to enhance the quality of life, appreciate their unique journey during the beautiful stages of age and for those in need while ensuring a compassionate and organized care experience.

SKILLS

- Delivering empathetic care and meaningful
- companionship.
- Provision of therapeutic services, calisthenics/exercises,

sports[swimming, badminton, volleyball, tennis].

- Dementia care, Stroke care, Mental health care, Person-centered care.
- Advanced communication, teamwork and relationship-building skills

Conducting audits, minimizing risks, and investigating with a keen eye.

- Experienced with CPR and First Aid delivery
- Critical thinking and problem-solving skills

EXPERIENCE

Precious Jewel Elderly care Homes/ Wellcare Home Medicals Limited — Residential and Domiciliary Caregiver.

NOVEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

- Deliver empathetic and personalized care to individuals, ensuring their physical and emotional well-being.
- Handled elders with dementia, mental illness, stroke and arthritis.
- Assisted with activities of daily living, including bathing, dressing, grooming, feeding and medication management.
- Maintained detailed records to track health progress and communicate effectively with the healthcare team.
- Offered companionship, therapeutic advice and conversations and engaged in meaningful conversations to alleviate feelings of loneliness and isolation.

Nouvelle Parfumrie Gandour[Natural Beauty Limited], Lagos state. — Admin & HR Officer

JANUARY 2023 - SEPTEMBER 2023

Resolved clients and employees requests and complaints.

- Prepared regular reports on expenses and office budgets for effective financial management.
- Managed staff data and records, ensuring accuracy and confidentiality.
- Evaluated and managed the recruitment process, demonstrating expertise in candidate assessment.
- Administered employees pay, benefits, and leave, ensuring compliance with organizational policies.

Total Health Trust Limited, Lagos state. — Risk and Compliance Officer[Intern]

NOVEMBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2022

- Conducted compliance audits minimizing risk and ensuring adherence to policies and regulations.
- Monitored departmental performances and standard operating procedures to minimize company risks.
- Collaboratively reviewed acts, policies, and procedures to improve service delivery.
- Investigated fraud cases within the company and health providers, demonstrating a keen eye for detail.
- Managed all customer interactions in relation to issuing claim applications and approvals.

EDUCATION

University of Ibadan, Ibadan, Oyo state.

B.ED. HUMAN KINETICS AND HEALTH EDUCATION[HUMAN KINETICS MAJOR].

FEBRUARY 2016 - FEBRUARY 2020.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Deep Tissue Massage Techniques 2024

Cursa Online Learning

CPR, AED & First Aid (6 Category) 2024

Save a Life Certification by NHCPS

Professional Caregivers Training 2024

Nightingale's Caregiver Academy

Pathway to Care Programme 2024

Florence Academy

Jobberman Soft Skills Training 2022

VOLUNTEERING

PUBLIC RELATIONS OFFICER 2019 - 2020

Nigeria Association for Physical and Health Education, Recreation and Sport and Dance.

DANCE AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR AD-HOC 2018 - 2019

Nigeria Association for Physical and Health Education, Recreation and Sport and Dance.

COUNSELING/ FIRST AID OFFICER 2018 - 2019

Community High School, Saamonda.

SWIMMING INSTRUCTOR FOR CHILDREN 2022

Annyville Schools, Lagos.

REFERENCES

Available on request.